<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<generator>Easy Feed Editor</generator>
<title>news - davidstudios</title>
<description>news and updates and random shit about the davidstudios website</description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/news.html</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 23:13:38 GMT</pubDate>
<managingEditor>david</managingEditor>

<item>
<title>might come back to geometry dash after months</title>
<description><![CDATA[<h1>
	<font color="000000">might come back to geometry dash after months</font></h1>
<p>
	<font color="000000">First, here&#39;s a long story short about how I began making levels:</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">I first started making levels on GD since 2017-2018, back then, I didn&#39;t really know what was I doing with the editor and just messed around with it (no shit it was the first time for me using the editor). You can find my really old levels at my old GD account DavidStudios if you&#39;re that curious.<br />
	During 2019-2020, it&#39;s where I slowly began improving, with things like decorations, syncing, etc. Those levels I made at that time were at a GDPS I used to be in, (two of them, actually). I prefer not to mention their names. Funnily enough, I made those said levels entirely on a mobile device during that time.<br />
	In case if you&#39;re wondering, I don&#39;t really play any GDPS anymore, I just prefer to stick to the OG game (cuz i&#39;m cool like that!!!!).<br />
	Anyways, around 2021, or late 2020 is where I actually began improving a whole lot. Unfortunately for whatever god forsaken reason I wasn&#39;t able to get those levels done at that time, blame my lack of motivation. However, I did upload a few unfinished levels I made during that time in which I never felt like finishing them. You can find those at my &quot;new&quot; account David1822.<br />
	Around 2022 is where I had actual motivation to finish a level at least <i>once</i>, the first level I finished in question is Vibes (correct me if that isn&#39;t the first level i finished please i don&#39;t remember lol). Ever since then, I wanted to make more levels and actually finishing them, just rarely, and also because people seemed to like my levels, which makes me happy.</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">But now, here&#39;s the REAL news:</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">On april of this year, I lost my current account (David1822) for... a couple of reasons:</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">1) My old laptop was shitty and we had to take it at a repair shop because of it, apparently they had to reset it for some reason that I forgot<br />
	2) I do not remember my password nor my e-mail at <i>all</i> (yes you can laugh at me now)<br />
	</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">Because of that, I &quot;stopped&quot; playing the game for months.</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">Though after some thinking, I might come back to this game with a level called Fresh New Start to start a new era for me and this game in some way, and I plan to finish it before new years eve (i hope).<br />
	The downside is, I have to start all over again with a new account as much as it sucks, since I couldn&#39;t find any way to get my other account back (DavidStuds is the new account if you wanna send it a friend request).<br />
	Don&#39;t expect me to fully come back as I&#39;m still debating, I just said that I <i><b>might</b></i>.</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">Apart from all this bullshit, I made an animations page where, of course, you can watch animations that I made throughout the years (they&#39;re not very good though). Go search it on the Random Bullshit page. </font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">i still don&#39;t have a way to end this post so thank you for reading all this yappering and good afternoon</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">- David ₍^. .^₎⟆</font></p>
]]></description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/posts/post4.html</link>
<author>david</author>
<guid  isPermaLink="false">41a67817-0113-459f-b6d6-10e9ae908a69</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 23:13:37 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>coming out (again)</title>
<description><![CDATA[<h1>
	<font color="000000">coming out (again)</font></h1>
<p>
	<font color="000000">i&#39;ve been bisexual for about 4 years and felt comfortable with staying like that, but here&#39;s the thing:</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">so recently i&#39;ve been doing some thinking if i might be pansexual for the past few days<br />
	mostly because i like people of any gender and i might actually be attracted to all genders, and also because i think it just feels right for me</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">but now after some thinking, i think it&#39;s safe to say for me that i am now officially pansexual!<br />
	this might sound a bit corny, but i do hope you guys are fine with this decision, and still accept me as a person<br />
	i will wait and see what it feels like to be pan as time goes on<br />
	(also yes this also means i love frying pans!!!!! /silly)</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">idk a way to end this post so uhhh Glorb i guess</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">- David ₍^. .^₎⟆</font></p>
]]></description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/posts/post3.html</link>
<author>david</author>
<guid  isPermaLink="false">7f8f0480-6bb5-4690-b152-74b5b32aca3b</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 05:16:54 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>just a small site update...</title>
<description><![CDATA[<h1>
	<font color="000000">just a small site update...</font></h1>
<p>
	<font color="000000">what&#39;s the small site update in question you may ask? well, there&#39;s a few:<br />
	you can now submit your art for me on the fanart page, either via e-mail or one of my contacts</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">you can now subscribe to RSS feeds on certain pages<br />
	if you don&#39;t know what RSS is and how to &quot;subscribe&quot; to feeds, go to the home page and you&#39;ll see smth about feeds n shit at the bottom, then click on that lil tutorial i made</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">and finally, i changed the meta descriptions and titles (whatever the fuck you call them) for every page,<br />
	as well as updating David&#39;s and FMAJ&#39;s bios a bit, see them for yourself</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">that&#39;s all for now, thank you for coming to my ted talk</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">- David ₍^. .^₎⟆</font></p>
]]></description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/posts/post2.html</link>
<author>david</author>
<guid  isPermaLink="false">8e07812a-13d3-4570-855f-57302be98229</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:19:50 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>new website overhaul!</title>
<description><![CDATA[<h1>
	<font color="000000">new website overhaul!</font></h1>
<p>
	<font color="000000">hello and welcome to the new web design!!</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">now there&#39;s:<br />
	1) NEW WEB DESIGN!!!<br />
	2) PAGES ARE A LOT MORE FORMAL THAN BEFORE!!!<br />
	3) REMOVED ALL THE USELESS SHIT FROM HERE!!!<br />
	4) SOME NEW PAGES!!!<br />
	5) GOODBYE DAVID DASH YOU WILL BE MISSED.</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">main reason i decided to change everything is because the old design looked shitty and there was some stuff that were pointless<br />
	this new design may not be amazing, but it&#39;s definitely an improvement compared to the last one lol<br />
	thank you for coming, i don&#39;t really have much to say xd<br />
	hope y&#39;all like this new overhaul tho!</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">- David ₍^. .^₎⟆</font></p>
]]></description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/posts/post1.html</link>
<author>david</author>
<guid  isPermaLink="false">4963ee65-4a5b-495a-8b8a-cbc9e9941bae</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:19:46 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>