<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<generator>Easy Feed Editor</generator>
<title>news - davidstudios</title>
<description>news and updates and random shit about the davidstudios website</description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/news.html</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
<managingEditor>david</managingEditor>

<item>
<title>just a small site update...</title>
<description><![CDATA[<h1>
	<font color="000000">just a small site update...</font></h1>
<p>
	<font color="000000">what&#39;s the small site update in question you may ask? well, there&#39;s a few:<br />
	you can now submit your art for me on the fanart page, either via e-mail or one of my contacts</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">you can now subscribe to RSS feeds on certain pages<br />
	if you don&#39;t know what RSS is and how to &quot;subscribe&quot; to feeds, go to the home page and you&#39;ll see smth about feeds n shit at the bottom, then click on that lil tutorial i made</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">and finally, i changed the meta descriptions and titles (whatever the fuck you call them) for every page,<br />
	as well as updating David&#39;s and FMAJ&#39;s bios a bit, see them for yourself</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">that&#39;s all for now, thank you for coming to my ted talk</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">- David ₍^. .^₎⟆</font></p>
]]></description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/posts/post2.html</link>
<author>david</author>
<guid  isPermaLink="false">8e07812a-13d3-4570-855f-57302be98229</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:19:50 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>new website overhaul!</title>
<description><![CDATA[<h1>
	<font color="000000">new website overhaul!</font></h1>
<p>
	<font color="000000">hello and welcome to the new web design!!</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">now there&#39;s:<br />
	1) NEW WEB DESIGN!!!<br />
	2) PAGES ARE A LOT MORE FORMAL THAN BEFORE!!!<br />
	3) REMOVED ALL THE USELESS SHIT FROM HERE!!!<br />
	4) SOME NEW PAGES!!!<br />
	5) GOODBYE DAVID DASH YOU WILL BE MISSED.</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">main reason i decided to change everything is because the old design looked shitty and there was some stuff that were pointless<br />
	this new design may not be amazing, but it&#39;s definitely an improvement compared to the last one lol<br />
	thank you for coming, i don&#39;t really have much to say xd<br />
	hope y&#39;all like this new overhaul tho!</font></p>
<p>
	<font color="000000">- David ₍^. .^₎⟆</font></p>
]]></description>
<link>https://itzdavidstudios.github.io/posts/post1.html</link>
<author>david</author>
<guid  isPermaLink="false">4963ee65-4a5b-495a-8b8a-cbc9e9941bae</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:19:46 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>